https://www.rackmountsales.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
JavaScript seems to be disabled in your browser.
You must have JavaScript enabled in your browser to utilize the functionality of this website.
Free Shipping on Rackmount Monitors 24/7 Phone Support at: 800-542-2489
Trustpilot
Login
Account
Cart
You have no items in your shopping cart.
Crystal Image Technologies
Search:
Special Promotion
1U 19" Rackmount Console, Diamond Series, 1280 X 1024, VGA Input (Part#DS-111-19)1U 17" Rackmount Monitor, 1280 X 1024, with 104 Key Notebook Keyboard - UL Certified (Part#RM-111-17)1U 17" Short Depth (17.3") Rackmount Monitor, 1280 X 1024 - UL Certified (Part#RM-111-17SD)1U 19" LCD Rackmount Monitor, Touchpad or Trackball (Part#RM-111-19)1U 19" Short Depth (18.9") Rackmount Monitor, Touchpad or Trackball - UL Certified (Part#RM-111-19SD)1U 19" Wide Screen Rackmount Monitor, 104 Key Notebook Keyboard-UL Certified (Part#RM-111-19W)1U 19" Rackmount Console, 1440 X 900, cUL Certified VGA & DVI Input, VGA & DVI Cables Included (Part#RM-111-19WH)1U 19" Short Depth (17.3") 1440 X 900 Console Drawer, UL Certified (Part#RM-111-19WHSD)8U 19" 1280 X 1024 Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-19)9U 20" 1600 X 1200 Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-20)8U 23" Wide Screen 1920 X 1080 HD Rackmount LCD Panel, VGA DVI HDMI Input (RMP-161-23)9U 24" Wide Screen 1920 X 1200 High Resolution Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-24)3U Dual 7" Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-77)6U 17" 1920 X 1080 Rackmount LCD Panel, VGA & DVI-D Input, In Stock (RMP-161-F17)8U 21.5" Wide Screen 1920 X 1080 Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-F21) 6U 17" 1920 X 1200 High Resolution Rackmount LCD Panel (RMP-161-X17) 1U 17" 1280 X 1024, Rack Mount LCD Drawer (Part#RMD-151-17)1U 17" Rackmount LCD Panel, Flip Down Rackmount Monitor Drawer (Part#RMD-151-17U)1U 19" Rackmount LCD Panel, Flip Up Rackmount Monitor Drawer (Part#RMD-151-19)1U 20" Rackmount LCD Monitor Drawer, No Keyboard, 1600 X 1200 (Part#RMD-151-20)1U 17" High Resolution (1920 X 1080) LCD Rackmount Drawer - (Part#RMD-151-F17)1U 17" High Resolution (1920 X 1200) LCD Rackmount Drawer - (Part#RMD-151-X17)2U 17" Triple 4K LCD Display Drawer, No Keyboard - (Part#RMD-X3K3)1U 17" 1280 X 1024 Short Depth Rackmount Monitor Drawer (Part#RMD-152-17)1U 17" DIamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 8 Port KVM Switch (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-08)1U 17" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 16 Port KVM Switch (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-16)1U 17" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor W/16 Port Cat5 KVM Switch -1 Local, 1 Remote Cat5 Console (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-16R)1U 17" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 32 Port KVM Switch (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-32)1U 17" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 16 Port KVM over IP Switch (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-IP16)1U 17" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 32 Port KVM Over IP Switch (Part#DS-147-17-Cat5-IP32)1U 19" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 16 Port KVM Switch (DS-147-19-Cat5-16)1U 19" Diamond Series Rackmount Monitor with Cat5 32 Port KVM Switch (Part#DS-147-19-Cat5-32)6' Cascade Cable for Cat5 and USB KVM swtiches (Part#Cascade Cat5/USB)PS/2 Dongle for Cat5 KVM (Part#Cat5 Dongle PS/2)VGA / USB Dongle for Cat5 KVM Switch (Part#Cat5 Dongle USB)DVI / USB Dongle for Cat5 KVM Switch (Part#Cat5 Dongle USB/DVI)Cat5 8 Port KVM Switch (Part#Cat5-08)8 Port Cat5 KVM Switch, 1 Local, 1 Remote Cat5 Console (Part#Cat5-08R)Cat5 16 Port KVM Switch (Part#Cat5-16)Cat5 16 Port KVM Switch with 1 local & 1 remote console (Part#Cat5-16R)1U Keyboard Drawer, 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Touchpad or Trackball, USB Cable (Part#RMD-183)1U Rackmount Keyboard Drawer - 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Short Depth (Part#RMD-184)1U Optical Mouse Keyboard Drawer, 88 Key Keyboard (Part#RMD-187)1U Rackmount Keyboard Drawer - 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Touchpad or Trackball, with 8 Port USB KVM Switch (Part#RMD-191-801)1U Rackmount Keyboard Drawer - 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Touchpad or Trackball, with 8 Port COMBO USB/PS2 KVM Switch (Part#RMD-191-Cat5-08)1U MAC Keyboard Drawer, Touchpad or Trackball, COMBO PS/2 USB Cable (Part#RMD-MAC)1U MAC Short Depth Keyboard Drawer, Touchpad or Trackball, COMBO PS/2 USB Cable (Part#RMD-MAC)6ft Keyboard Cable for RMD-183 & RMD-184 (Part#KB-6)2U 17" Triple 4K LCD Display Drawer, No Keyboard - (Part#RMD-X3K3)6U 4K 17" Rackmount LCD Panel, Display Port 1.2 + HDMI 1.4 + Stereo Speakers (Part# RMP-161-17K)1U 17" 4K (3840 X 2160) Rackmount Monitor (15.7" to 31.7" Mounting Range)
- (Part# RM-K17USD )1U 17" 4K LCD Rackmount Drawer - (Part#RMD-151-K17)2U 17" 4K Triple LCD Rackmount Display Console - (Part#RM-X3K3)9U 4K 23.8" Rackmount LCD Panel, Display Port 1.2 & HDMI 1.4 Input (Part# RMP-161-24K)1U 24" 4K Rackmount Monitor, 3840 X 2160, supports 1920 X 1200 & 1080p HD - (Part#RM-K24)1U 17" 4K (3840 X 2160) Rackmount Monitor (18.5" to 31.5" Mounting Range)
- (Part#RM-117K)15" High Brightness Marine Bridge LCD Panel 1024 X 768 (MB-15H)17" Marine Grade LCD Panel 1280 X 1024 (MB-17)17" High Brightness Marine Grade LCD Panel 1280 X 1024 (MB-17H)17" High Resolution Marine Grade LCD Panel 1920 X 1080 (MB-17W)17" High Resolution, High Brightness - Marine Grade LCD Panel 1920 X 1080 (MB-17WH)15" Wide Screen Marine Grade LCD Panel 1366 X 768 (MB-15W)19" Marine Grade LCD Panel 1280 X 1024, IEC60945 Certified (MB-19)19" High Brightness Marine Grade LCD Panel 1280 X 1024, IEC6095 (Part#MB-19H)1U 17" High Brightness Rackmount Monitor, 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Touchpad or Trackball (Part#RMH-111-17)1U 19" High Brightness Rackmount Monitor, 104 Key Notebook Keyboard, Touchpad or Trackball (Part#RMH-111-19)1U 17" High Brightness LCD Rackmount Monitor W/ 8 Port COMBO USB/PS2 KVM, SUN & iMAC Compatible (Part#RMH-182-17-801)1U 19" High Brightness LCD Rackmount Monitor W/ 8 Port COMBO USB/PS2 KVM, SUN & iMAC Compatible (Part#RMH-182-19-801)1U 17" High Brightness Rackmount LCD Panel, Rackmount Monitor Drawer (RMHD-151-17)1U 19" High Brightness Rackmount LCD Panel, Rackmount Monitor Drawer (RMHD-151-19)7U 17" Rackmount LCD Panel - High Brightness (Part#RMPH-161-17)8U 19" Rackmount LCD Panel - High Brightness (Part#RMPH-161-19)1U Sun 17" LCD Rackmount Monitor - UL Certified (Part# SUN-117)1U Sun 17" LCD Rackmount Monitor with 16 Port USB KVM (Part# SUN-117-16)1U Sun 17" LCD Rackmount Monitor with 8 Port USB KVM (Part# SUN-117-8)1U Sun 19" LCD Rackmount Monitor (Part# SUN-119)1U Sun 19" LCD Rackmount Monitor with KVM (Part# SUN-119-16)1U Sun 19" LCD Rackmount Monitor with KVM (Part# SUN-119-8)2U Sun 17" LCD Rackmount Monitor, Seperate Sliding Keyboard and Monitor (Part#SUN-217)2U Sun 17" LCD Rackmount Monitor with 16 Port KVM (Part# SUN-217-16)17" Rugged 1920 X 1080 LCD Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-F17)21" Rugged LCD Panel, 1920 X 1080 Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-F21)19" Rugged Aluminum Frame, 1440 X 900 - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-W19)27" Wide Screen, Rugged Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-W27)32" Wide Screen, Rugged Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-W32)40" Wide Screen, Rugged Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-W40)46" Wide Screen, Rugged Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-W46)17" 1920 X 1200, LCD Aluminum Frame - Industrial LCD Panel (Part# LCD-AP-X17)2U 17" Triple 4K LCD Display Drawer, No Keyboard - (Part#RMD-X3K3)17" 2U Dual LCD Display Drawer FHD / 1080p - (Part#RMD-151-X17Ax2)17" 2U Dual LCD Rackmount Monitor - Dual Slide Keyboard/LCD FHD / 1080p - (Part#RM-X17DAx2)17" 2U Triple LCD Rackmount Monitor - Dual Slide Keyboard/LCD FHD / 1080p - (Part#RM-X17DAx3)17" 2U Triple LCD Display Drawer FHD / 1080p - (Part#RMD-151-X17Ax3)2U 17" 4K Triple LCD Rackmount Display Console - (Part#RM-X3K3)2U 24" Dual LCD Display Drawer FHD / 1080p - (Part#RMD-151-24Ax2)2U 17" Triple LCD Display Drawer, (1080p) No Keyboard - (Part#RMD-F17-3)1U 19" Rackmount LCD Drawer with Integrated Quad Split Screen (Part# RMD-151-19QD)1U 20" Rackmount LCD Drawer with Integrated Quad Split Screen (Part# RMD-151-20QD)1U 19" Wide Screen Rackmount LCD Panel, Flip Up Monitor Drawer with Integrated Quad Split Screen (Part#RMDW-151-19QD)9U 19" Rackmount LCD Panel with Integrated Quad Split Screen (Part# RMP-161-19QD)10U 20" Rackmount LCD Panel with Integrated Quad Split Screen (Part# RMP-161-20QD)8U 19" Wide Screen (1440 X 900) LCD Panel with integrated Quad Split Screen (Part# RMPW-161-19QD)9U 21.5" (1920 X 1080) Rackmount LCD Panel - Quad Display (Part# RMP-161-F21QD)1U 12 Outlet Metered PDU -
20Amp, 110V
- 12, 5-20R / 5-20P (Part# H12US-20A-MD/CR_520)12 Outlet Rack Mount Metered PDU -
30Amp, 110V
- 12, 5-20R, 5-30P (Part# H12US-30A-MD/F)8 Outlet Rack Mount Metered PDU -
20Amp, 110V - 8 5-20R, 5-20P PDU (Part# H8US-20A-MD/F)Smart PDU - Vertical 20Amp, 110V - Monitored PDU - 24 5-20R, 5-20P PDU (Part# V24US-20A-MT)Vertical Smart PDU -
20Amp, 110V - Metered PDU - 8, 5-20R, 5-20P PDU (Part# V8US-20A-MD/F)2U W Series - KWh Monitored PDU, 20, 5-20R Outlets, 110V/20A With L-520 Locking Plug (Part# H20US-20A-W/CR_L520-3B-1)IP Dongle for Monitored PDU (1 Dongle can control up to 16 PDU's)
Part# IPD-02-S)Blanking Panel - 1U Rackmount Steel Blanking Panel (Part# BP1U)Blanking Panel - 2U Rackmount Steel Blanking Panel (Part# BP2U)Blanking Panel - 3U Rackmount Steel Blanking Panel (Part# BP3U)Blanking Panel - 4U Rackmount Steel Blanking Panel (Part# BP4U)1U Hinged Wall Mount Bracket (Part#HWB-1U)2U Hinged Wall Mount Bracket (Part#HWB-2U)4U Hinged Wall Mount Bracket (Part#HWB-4U)6U Hinged Wall Mount Bracket (Part#HWB-6U)1U 19" Wide Screen Rackmount Monitor, 104 Key Notebook Keyboard-UL Certified (Part#RM-111-19W)1U 24" 1920 X 1200 High Resolution LCD Rackmount Monitor - (Part#RM-X24)1U 21.5" 1920 X 1080 1080p LCD Rackmount Monitor - (Part#RM-F21)1U 21.5" Rotating 1920 X 1200 LCD Rackmount Monitor - (Part#RM-F21A-R)1U 24" 4K Rackmount Monitor, 3840 X 2160, supports 1920 X 1200 & 1080p HD - (Part#RM-K24)1U 24" Rotating 1920 X 1200 LCD Rackmount Monitor - (Part#RM-F24A-R)1U 24" Rotating 4K LCD Rackmount Monitor - (Part#RM-K24A-R)1U 24" Rotating 4K Rackmount LCD Drawer, No Keyboard - (Part#RMD-151-K24A-R)
Our Guarantee
Blog
Contact Us
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on the site, place an order, enter a contest or sweepstakes, respond to a survey or communication such as e-mail, or participate in another site feature.
When ordering or registering, we may ask you for your name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number, credit card information or other information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
We also collect information about gift recipients so that we can fulfill the gift purchase. The information we collect about gift recipients is not used for marketing purposes.
Like many websites, we use "cookies" to enhance your experience and gather information about visitors and visits to our websites. Please refer to the "Do we use 'cookies'?" section below for information about cookies and how we use them.
How do we use your information?We may use the information we collect from you when you register, purchase products, enter a contest or promotion, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:
To personalize your site experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.
To quickly process your transactions.
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.
If you have opted-in to receive our e-mail newsletter, we may send you periodic e-mails. If you would no longer like to receive promotional e-mail from us, please refer to the "How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?" section below. If you have not opted-in to receive e-mail newsletters, you will not receive these e-mails. Visitors who register or participate in other site features such as marketing programs and 'members-only' content will be given a choice whether they would like to be on our e-mail list and receive e-mail communications from us.
How do we protect visitor information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information. Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. When you place orders or access your personal information, we offer the use of a secure server. All sensitive/credit information you supply is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our databases to be only accessed as stated above.Do we use "cookies"?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies. If you turn cookies off, you won't have access to many features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone by contacting customer service.Do we disclose the information we collect to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information unless we provide you with advance notice, except as described below. The term "outside parties" does not include Crystal Image Technologies. It also does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property, or safety.However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.How can you opt-out, remove or modify information you have provided to us?To modify your e-mail subscriptions, please let us know by modifying your preferences in the "My Account" section. Please note that due to email production schedules you may receive any emails already in production.To delete all of your online account information from our database, sign into the "My Account" section of our site and remove your shipping addresses, billing addresses & payment information. Please note that we may maintain information about an individual sales transaction in order to service that transaction and for record keeping.Third party linksIn an attempt to provide you with increased value, we may include third party links on our site. These linked sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these linked sites (including if a specific link does not work).Changes to our policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. Policy changes will apply only to information collected after the date of the change. This policy was last modified on October 25, 2006.Questions and feedbackWe welcome your questions, comments, and concerns about privacy. Please send us any and all feedback pertaining to privacy, or any other issue.Online Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Terms and ConditionsPlease also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.
Site Map
Search Terms
Advanced Search
Orders and Returns
Contact Us
COMPANY
Home
About Us
Copyright © 2006-2019 Crystal Image Technologies, All Rights Reserved.
